[{
        "question": "1.Which of the following is not an Operating System ?",
        "options": [
            "Windows",
            "Linux",
            "DOS",
            "Oracle"
        ],
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "2.When was the first Operating System is developed ? ",
        "options": [
            "1940",
            "1945",
            "1950",
            "1955"
        ],
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "3.What is the meaning of the Booting in Operating System ?",
        "options": [
            "Restart the System",
            "Install the Program",
            "Scanning the System",
            "Turning off the System"
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "4.Which of the following is not a part of the Operating System ?",
        "options": [
            "Input Output Control Program",
            "Job control program",
            "Supervisor",
            "Performance Monitor"
        ],
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "5.Which of the following is not an Algorithm of Operating System ?",
        "options": [
            "First Come First Serve Algorithm",
            "Brute Force Algorithm",
            "Round Robin Algorithm",
            "Shortest Job First Algorithm"
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "6.Which of the following is/are Open Source Operating System",
        "options": [
            "Linux",
            "Windows",
            "Both A and B",
            "Android"
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "7.Page fault is what ? ",
        "options": [
            "an Error in a specific page",
            "an access to a page not currently in a memory",
            "a Reference to a page belonging to another program",
            "occurs when a program accesses a page of memory"
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "8.Which one of the following errors will be handle by the operating system?",
        "options": [
            "lack of paper in printer",
            "connection failure in the network",
            "power failure",
            "all of the mentioned"
        ],
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "9.If a process fails, most operating system write the error information to a ______",
        "options": [
            "new file",
            "another running process",
            "log file",
            "none of the mentioned"
        ],
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "10.FIFO scheduling is a type of:",
        "options": [
            "pre-emptive scheduling",
            "non pre-emptive scheduling",
            "deadline scheduling",
            "none of the above"
        ],
        "answer": 2
    }
]